directrev.com 2015-12-31

# Privacy Policy - DirectREV - Media Delivery Platform

DirectREV believes in all Internet users' rights to privacy. DirectREV does not engage in any form of distribution or sale of Personally Identifiable Information to third parties for their own promotional use, including but not limited to, names, email/postal addresses, and phone numbers.

### Cookies

DirectREV uses session and persistent cookies, as well as web beacons on our website. These are needed for site navigation and to perform aggregate analysis of what is viewed on our site.

### Collection and Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Information

Like most standard website servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. Log file data may be retained for up to a maximum period of twelve months.

### Collection and Use of Personally Identifiable Information

Registering to become a member of the DirectREV online advertising network, either as an advertiser or a publisher, requires the submission of Personally Identifiable information to our company. This can include your full name, mailing and/or billing address, email address, company name, and website URL. We use this information to service your accounts and respond to inquiries. Communications to our business users are related to the Advertising Network. We hold all such information submitted in strict confidence.

### Disclosure of your information

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as submitting email communications to you on our behalf. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We may also disclose your personal information:  

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request
  * if we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in
  * ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so

### Access to your information

If your personal information changes you may update or correct it by contacting us through our online form. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

### Retention of data collected through our website

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact us through our online form. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure.

Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, please contact us using our online form.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

DirectREV may find it necessary to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any changes will be posted at this site. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective.

### Other information

Our site may includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of DirectREV. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any website you visit.

With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us using our online form.

Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us using our online form

### Contact Us

To inquire about privacy concerns, please contact DirectREV using our online form.
